[
    {
        "front": "Kore, Kono",
        "back": "This (near to the speaker)",
        "chapter": 4
    },
    {
        "front": "Sore, Sono",
        "back": "That (near to the listener)",
        "chapter": 4
    },
    {
        "front": "Are, Ano",
        "back": "That over there (far from both listener & speaker)",
        "chapter": 4
    },
    {
        "front": "Dore, Dono",
        "back": "Which",
        "chapter": 4
    },
    {
        "front": "Hon",
        "back": "Book",
        "chapter": 4
    },
    {
        "front": "Fairu",
        "back": "File",
        "chapter": 4
    },
    {
        "front": "Tsukue",
        "back": "Table",
        "chapter": 4
    },
    {
        "front": "Isu",
        "back": "Chair",
        "chapter": 4
    },
    {
        "front": "Biru",
        "back": "Building",
        "chapter": 4
    },
    {
        "front": "Nan",
        "back": "What",
        "chapter": 4
    },
    {
        "front": "Deskara",
        "back": "Therefore",
        "chapter": 4
    },
    {
        "front": "Tokei",
        "back": "Watch, Clock",
        "chapter": 4
    },
    {
        "front": "Sō des ne ",
        "back": "That’s right",
        "chapter": 4
    },
    {
        "front": "Kasa ",
        "back": "Umbrella",
        "chapter": 4
    },
    {
        "front": "Sugoi",
        "back": "Wonderful, amazing",
        "chapter": 4
    },
    {
        "front": "Dōzo",
        "back": "Please (While offering something to someone)",
        "chapter": 4
    },
    {
        "front": "Arigatō",
        "back": "Casual way of saying thanks",
        "chapter": 4
    },
    {
        "front": "Yo",
        "back": "(When spoken in the end) Making an appeal to someone",
        "chapter": 4
    },
    {
        "front": "Etto",
        "back": "Umm...",
        "chapter": 4
    },
    {
        "front": "Koko; Kochira",
        "back": "Here; (Polite)",
        "chapter": 4
    },
    {
        "front": "Soko; Sochira",
        "back": "There; (Polite)",
        "chapter": 4
    },
    {
        "front": "Asoko; Achira",
        "back": "Over There; (Polite)",
        "chapter": 4
    },
    {
        "front": "Doko; Dochira",
        "back": "Where; (Polite)",
        "chapter": 4
    },
    {
        "front": "Jimushitsu",
        "back": "Office room ",
        "chapter": 4
    },
    {
        "front": "Uketsuke",
        "back": "Reception",
        "chapter": 4
    },
    {
        "front": "Kaigishitsu",
        "back": "Meeting room",
        "chapter": 4
    },
    {
        "front": "Kaidan",
        "back": "Stairs",
        "chapter": 4
    },
    {
        "front": "Denwa",
        "back": "Telephone",
        "chapter": 4
    },
    {
        "front": "Erebeta",
        "back": "Lift",
        "chapter": 4
    },
    {
        "front": "Iriguchi",
        "back": "Entrance",
        "chapter": 4
    },
    {
        "front": "Deguchi",
        "back": "Exit",
        "chapter": 4
    },
    {
        "front": "Shokudō",
        "back": "Canteen",
        "chapter": 4
    },
    {
        "front": "Ue",
        "back": "Above",
        "chapter": 4
    },
    {
        "front": "Shita",
        "back": "Below",
        "chapter": 4
    },
    {
        "front": "Soto",
        "back": "Outside",
        "chapter": 4
    },
    {
        "front": "Naka",
        "back": "Inside",
        "chapter": 4
    },
    {
        "front": "Hana ",
        "back": "Flowers",
        "chapter": 4
    },
    {
        "front": "Neko",
        "back": "Cat",
        "chapter": 4
    },
    {
        "front": "Inu",
        "back": "Dog",
        "chapter": 4
    },
    {
        "front": "Ie",
        "back": "House",
        "chapter": 4
    },
    {
        "front": "Shachō",
        "back": "President",
        "chapter": 4
    },
    {
        "front": "Kaichō",
        "back": "Chairman",
        "chapter": 4
    },
    {
        "front": "Buchō",
        "back": "Manager",
        "chapter": 4
    },
    {
        "front": "Denwa Bangō",
        "back": "Landline No.",
        "chapter": 4
    },
    {
        "front": "Keitai",
        "back": "Mobile No.",
        "chapter": 4
    },
    {
        "front": "Seki",
        "back": "Seat",
        "chapter": 4
    },
    {
        "front": "Nōto",
        "back": "Notebook",
        "chapter": 4
    },
    {
        "front": "Techō",
        "back": "Pocket Diary",
        "chapter": 4
    },
    {
        "front": "Meishi",
        "back": "Visiting Card",
        "chapter": 4
    },
    {
        "front": "Zasshi",
        "back": "Magazine",
        "chapter": 4
    },
    {
        "front": "Jidōsha",
        "back": "Automobile",
        "chapter": 4
    },
    {
        "front": "Kasa",
        "back": "Umbrella",
        "chapter": 4
    },
    {
        "front": "Kagi",
        "back": "Keys",
        "chapter": 4
    },
    {
        "front": "Shin Ōsaka",
        "back": "(Place Name)",
        "chapter": 4
    },
    {
        "front": "Otearai",
        "back": "Washroom",
        "chapter": 4
    },
    {
        "front": "Jimusho",
        "back": "Office",
        "chapter": 4
    },
    {
        "front": "Erebeta",
        "back": "Lift",
        "chapter": 4
    },
    {
        "front": "Kuni",
        "back": "(Your) country",
        "chapter": 4
    },
    {
        "front": "Kutsu",
        "back": "Shoes",
        "chapter": 4
    },
    {
        "front": "Keshōshitsu",
        "back": "Make-Up Room",
        "chapter": 4
    }
]